[{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680581480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":18331,"timeElapsed":1794564},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680599578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":18096,"timeElapsed":1812663},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680932063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":332483,"timeElapsed":2145148},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680939366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7301,"timeElapsed":2152451},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680944430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5063,"timeElapsed":2157515},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680948209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3777,"timeElapsed":2161294},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680950468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2256,"timeElapsed":2163553},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680959851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9381,"timeElapsed":2172936},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680968363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8510,"timeElapsed":2181448},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680979072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9483,"timeElapsed":2192157},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680982058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2984,"timeElapsed":2195143},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680986750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4690,"timeElapsed":2199835},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681035196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":48444,"timeElapsed":2248281},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681041670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6471,"timeElapsed":2254755},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681045256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":2258341},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681054324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9067,"timeElapsed":2267409},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681057810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3484,"timeElapsed":2270895},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681060899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":2273984},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681075346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7975,"timeElapsed":2288431},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681077637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2289,"timeElapsed":2290722},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681081260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3621,"timeElapsed":2294345},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681084155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2893,"timeElapsed":2297240},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681087085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2929,"timeElapsed":2300170},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681089192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2105,"timeElapsed":2302277},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681091415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":2304500},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681093802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2385,"timeElapsed":2306887},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681096163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2360,"timeElapsed":2309248},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681116519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":19204,"timeElapsed":2329604},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681121856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5335,"timeElapsed":2334941},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681131428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9570,"timeElapsed":2344513},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681135068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":2348153},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681163827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":28757,"timeElapsed":2376912},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681166206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2378,"timeElapsed":2379291},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681170872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4664,"timeElapsed":2383956},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681176683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5810,"timeElapsed":2389768},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681179875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3190,"timeElapsed":2392959},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681196193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":15327,"timeElapsed":2409278},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681200591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4395,"timeElapsed":2413676},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681205582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4989,"timeElapsed":2418667},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681208823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3240,"timeElapsed":2421908},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681213511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":2426596},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681218424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4910,"timeElapsed":2431509},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681221296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":2434381},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681223593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2296,"timeElapsed":2436678},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681227822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4227,"timeElapsed":2440907},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681237781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6634,"timeElapsed":2450865},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681239716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":2452801},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681243454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3735,"timeElapsed":2456539},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681245139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1682,"timeElapsed":2458224},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681257253,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":12113,"timeElapsed":2470338},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681262163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4908,"timeElapsed":2475248},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681264013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":2477098},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681266794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":2479878},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681272073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5278,"timeElapsed":2485158},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681273446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1371,"timeElapsed":2486531},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681281783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7175,"timeElapsed":2494868},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681284228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":2497313},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681289197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4967,"timeElapsed":2502282},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681291934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":2505019},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681294755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":2507840},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681298363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3605,"timeElapsed":2511448},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681301407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3042,"timeElapsed":2514492},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681304903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":2517988},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681306975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2070,"timeElapsed":2520060},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681315050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6598,"timeElapsed":2528135},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681316972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1921,"timeElapsed":2530057},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681321954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4980,"timeElapsed":2535039},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681325202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3247,"timeElapsed":2538287},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681328247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3043,"timeElapsed":2541332},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681332955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4706,"timeElapsed":2546040},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681335041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2084,"timeElapsed":2548126},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681338704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":2551789},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681341430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2725,"timeElapsed":2554515},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681360932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":18472,"timeElapsed":2574017},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681363145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":2576230},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681365686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2539,"timeElapsed":2578771},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681367959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":2581044},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681372181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4220,"timeElapsed":2585266},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681374739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2556,"timeElapsed":2587824},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681380285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5544,"timeElapsed":2593370},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681382248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1962,"timeElapsed":2595333},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681384410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2160,"timeElapsed":2597495},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681387433,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":2600518},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681394316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5982,"timeElapsed":2607400},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681396575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2257,"timeElapsed":2609660},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681400321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3745,"timeElapsed":2613406},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681402347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2024,"timeElapsed":2615432},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681407333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4984,"timeElapsed":2620418},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681409393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2058,"timeElapsed":2622478},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681412272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2878,"timeElapsed":2625357},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681414882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":2627967},{"subjectID":"qvrpbp48sm","prolificID":"63474e67a5fd298c6103c409","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3902b6827a5af08dcd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735681417475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2591,"timeElapsed":2630560}]